Way to destroy your reputation.
(Sheldon:)You see? People have been pointing
and laughing at me all morning.
It's not true.
(Sheldon:)People have been pointing and laughing
at you your whole life.
(Sheldon:)All right, I've had enough.
Attention, everyone.
I'm Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
(Sheldon:)As many of you
in the Physics Department know...
(Sheldon:)...my career trajectory
has taken a minor detour.
Off a cliff.
(Sheldon:)-My credibility may have been damaged.
-Completely wrecked.
(Sheldon:)But I would like to remind you that in
science there's no such thing as failure.
(Sheldon:)There once was a man...
(Sheldon:)...who referred to his prediction
of a cosmological constant...
(Sheldon:)...as the single biggest blunder
of his career.
(Sheldon:)That man's name was, surprise, surprise,
Albert Einstein.
Yeah, but research into dark energy
proved...
...Einstein's cosmological constant
was actually right all along.
So you're still, surprise, surprise,
a loser.